Anusha Konchada

anushakonchada@gmail.com | +1 (623)-215-5033

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/anushakonchada

Summary: Over 10+ years of IT experience mainly in **Business Analysis, Automation Testing and Project Management** all along within **Deloitte Consulting**. Engaged with multiple Health Care, Insurance Retail clients to identify the business need for transformation and the impact of technology changes.

Recognized for my strong people management skills to deliver work in multiple modernization initiatives, Core Business transformations includes various types of testing.

Skills

Programming Languages	Core Java, Python, Gherkin, SQL
Test Automation &	Selenium Web driver, Cucumber (Behavior Driven Development), TestNG, Junit, Pytest, REST Assured API,
Frameworks	Data Driven, Page Object Model, Keyword Driven, Hybrid frameworks, UI Path
IDE	Eclipse, IntelliJ, PyCharm
Version Control, Build CI-CD	GIT, Tortoise SVN, Maven, Team City, Jenkins
Databases	Microsoft SQL server, MySQL, Neo4J, MongoDB
Project Management	HP ALM, Confluence, JIRA, Rational Test Center (RTC), Rational Quality Manager (RQM), IBM Rational Team
	Concert, IBM Rational Requirement Composer, Service Now
Containerization	Docker, Docker Swarm, Kubernetes
API Testing	Postman, Swagger
Industry Domain knowledge	US Health Care (Claims in-take, Care: Utilization Management, Provider Systems, Health Insurance- Integrated Eligibility), Retail (Customer Experience), Auto, Property & Casualty Insurance, Banking- Fees Reinstatement
Software Methodologies	Agile, Waterfall
Other Technologies	PEGA (CRM & BPM), Guidewire Insurance Suite (Policy, Billing, Claims Center, DataHub)
Certifications	Oracle Certified Java Professional SE 6, ISTQB

Work Experience within Deloitte

End-to-End Lead & Business Analyst, Client: Kroger (Sept 2019- Aug 2020)

- Engaged with Technology and Business SMEs to gather requirements to re-engineer and build an updated Promotion
 Exchange Engine (PXE) to replace their Legacy system hosted through Point-of-Sale, eliminates the 3-month wait to reflect
 their newly added functional changes for offers each time and also, upgrade their Architectural design as well
- Led End to End testing in Customer Experience space to deliver **50+ Regression scenarios** for two Critical Customer facing portals, includes gathering Business rules and creating E2E Regression **Automation Test Cases using Selenium** in Agile
- Managed and executed 100+ E2E Regression scenarios to validate Coupons, offers and Messages features built to be
 Client's in-house Promotion Execution Engine that was rolled out to 2500+ stores across US. The advent of Automated
 Regression cycles not only brought down the defect count by multifold and shortened the engineering cycles

Test Manager & Functional Lead, Client: Anthem Health Care (Sept 2017- Aug 2019)

- Managed a 20-member team through 14 test cycles (like Functional Regression, SIT, UAT, Do No Harm, and End-to-End) consists of 6000+ tests for 6 crucial enterprises releases with focus on validating the two custom solutions that empowered the customers to use the Modernized solution and get away with the legacy solution which resulted in improved & better user experience, saved crucial time with the use of easy workflow implemented in PEGA
- Led sessions with Business and Technology SMEs to define the future state Claims Intake and Workflow solution. Analysed
 categorization and prioritization needs across multiple platforms to define business consolidating stand-alone legacy
 Mainframe processing systems into the target PEGA platform
- Led Daily **Scrum** and implemented effective onshore-offshore hand off processes(multiple), resulting in 25% increase in the throughput. Additionally, assisted with the automation of the post code deployment smoke testing, which eliminated 5 hours per week manual effort
- Led multiple initiatives within the testing team alongside coordinating with multiple Anthem support teams such as Test Data Management, Automatic Provisioning Tool (APT), Boundary System App owners, Daily Drive Defect Triage meetings at Enterprise level for various Test cycles using **JIRA**

Business Analyst, Client: Pekin Insurance (Feb 2017 - Aug 2017)

• Gathered requirements for 15 Reports & Downstream data feeds to help the client build its own integrated Policy Administration System using **Guidewire** implementation

- Led several meetings with several Business stakeholders, Centers (policy, Claims, Billing) threads to track and collate the extensions which were potential field dependencies for important data modelling phase
- Performed Data Analysis alongside with Data Architects, Data profiling, tracked dependencies from other tracks which
 was a critical pre-requisite design effort prior to the implementation phase that saved crucial hours for engineering team.
 This involved mapping fields from Guidewire to DataHub and InfoCenter (DH and IC are Guidewire products) to ensure
 the completeness of Data modelling for the reports
- Performed a **Proof of Concept** to gauge the performance of Contact Manager Conversions through **Automation** (using Selenium in JAVA) and presented it to the leadership which not only saved time but also delineated the results

Automation Test Lead & Functional Analyst, Client: California State Automobile Association (July 2014- Jan 2017)

- Led the Automation team for Auto and Property Insurance products during multiple releases to automate more than 10000+ test cases across releases and designed policy life cycle approach for end to end testing that enabled Client convert 625K policies from legacy Policy Administration System (PAS) to Exigen's Platform with which the client was primarily able to retain integrated view of their varied businesses
- Functioned as SME for Automation, acquired deep knowledge of PAS requirements and extensive hands-on experience
 to automate the test cases using Exigen's Selenium framework configured run through Jenkins for CI/CD helped report
 critical defects during periodic enhancements each release
- Coordinated with the client's business team for requirement clarification, walkthrough of the test scenarios & business sign-off on the test scenarios, and worked with system owners for interface signoffs across all the PAS Releases

Developer, Client: Providence of Rhode Island (Feb'13 – May'14)

- Created 50 story boards for various modules that led to identification of numerous functional gaps at an early stage. Led the Functional team for the module and followed up with the Functional SME for clarifications to implement the delta changes and performed peer reviews within Team to suggest the best possible solution as needed
- Led a team of 10 members in converting the business rules from legacy implementation to the **Oracle Policy Automation** (**OPA**) rule engine that helped accurately determine the eligibility of the household to receive the benefits

Functional Analyst, Client: Bank of America (Aug '11 – Jan'13)

- Created Test Plan, Test Scenarios, Test Cases, and Requirement Traceability Matrix (RTM) documents and identify test data to condition data for System Integration Testing (SIT) and Regression phases for the Fees Reinstatement project
- Created and enhanced SQL scripts aimed at data quality validation scripts and check functional consistency of the data across the system and assisted onshore team in planning and execution of E2E Testing of the application
- Collaborated across different hierarchies in the organization for end to end communication and daily/ weekly status updates and trained new team members to bring them up to the speed for execution phase on iSeries AS400

Test Analyst, Client: IBM Global International Assignment Management System (July '10 – July'11)

- Test case creation, execution, updating Test cases based on the Change Requests amidst of the Integration test cycle
- Timely workflow data validations using SQL Server interfaced via TOAD5.0 and accurate defect reporting in RQM helped the client implement their assignment management system for their workforce at their Organization level

Education

• Chaitanya Bharathi Institute of Technology, Osmania University (2010), Hyderabad, India
Bachelor of Engineering (Information Technology): Secured 3rd rank at Osmania University level in B.E.

Achievements & Firm Initiatives

Rewards and Recognition:

- Received more than 15 Applause and spot awards over the time for my contribution and instrumentalizing mentees at Firm
- Received personalized & Team appreciation emails from the Leadership within Firm, Clients and Vendors

Firm Initiatives:

- Led internal threads for the professionals to participate at External Conferences such as Star East Software Testing conference 2019, Building Business Capability Conference 2020; led many local chapters to help practitioners to socialize over networking events and volunteered for teaching at Government schools back in India
- Lead quintessential awareness sessions Globally under a Senior Partner in the Firm. Received appreciation for designing, planning and delivering these training sessions for more than 2 years
- Created multiple Quals to help Firm win the potential engagements and contributed with recruitment process at Analyst,
 Consultant level